This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
promise, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon.
Out on the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
The last of the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Off we go.
This is awesome every single time.
You said it.
Shadow of the Ring.
Oh yeah.
It's the Sharks of Merge.
Pedro and I will take care of
the mission, so don't you worry.
Sorry, Luffy.
I know I said I'd do this on my own, but
it looks like I'll be borrowing Brooke.
Infiltration is somewhat of
a specialty of mine, Pedro.
I'm sure I'll be of use to you.
I'll find that horny cliff
in a spooktacular fashion.
Sweet! Good luck!
I know you can handle this.
After we meet up with Sanji and Pudding,
we'll wait here for you to come back.
Be careful.
Things might get ugly.
That message from Peckham
still troubles me.
I know, but we kept going
anyway, so no regrets.
We're counting on you.
Have fun storming the castle!
You got this!
Okay, let's move.
Depth, 15 meters.
Visibility, good.
This is going well.
If we follow the river, we'll make
it straight to Big Mom's castle.
I hope the waters stay deep.
We'll make do.
Yeah, we made it!
Big Mom, you can't stop us now!
I smell an adventure!
We don't need one.
Let's just find Sanji,
then wait on the boat.
Hey! Sanji! Pudding!
We made it!
Just like you told us!
Stop shouting!
What if the enemy's here?
This is weird.
You said Sanji was just standing there?
You're sure? Uh, yeah.
I think I know Sanji.
Maybe he ran away, because I didn't
see him when I looked a second later.
Oh, wow!
Now we've got to eat the ground!
It's whipped cream only hard! Huh?
Um, you're right.
It tastes like meringue.
So this island is all candy, too? What?
I want to live here!
This was the spot!
Sanji was standing right
up here with Pudding, too.
But I looked away for just a
second, and then they were gone.
Well, this is definitely the coast
where Pudding told us to meet her.
I know you wouldn't lie about this,
but I don't know why they would
run off as soon as they spotted us.
I was so excited to see him, but now what?
What's up?
Hey! It's him!
Saji!
Saji! Huh?
Come back!
What happened? Wait!
Is he here?
He was, but he ran off!
Maybe he's playing a game!
Really?
Sanji!
Hey, wait! Where'd he go?
We lost him!
But this place sure looks delicious!
It's a forest of candies!
It smells good, too!
If all three of them saw him,
then he must be here somewhere.
But why would he run to the
forest without saying anything?
Did something happen?
I want you all to know this.
I never meant to hide anything
from my friends, okay?
I don't know.
Maybe he's just embarrassed.
Hey! Sanji!
Come on out!
We're here to pick you up! Sanji!
Okay, let's split up and search!
I'm going for the cakes!
We're searching by the cakes!
I'm going straight, straight to where
that awesome-looking caramel is!
Then I'm going to the jelly beans!
That looks like a good
place for Sanji, right?
No, you don't!
You'll get lost again!
Aw, come on!
It couldn't have gone that far!
Besides, what else are we supposed to do?
You're talking like people who are
about to get lost in the woods.
Besides,
it seems you're motivated by something
other than your desire to find Sanji.
What do you mean?
I promise, you're awful liars, okay?
Fine, let's all search together.
You can have snacks, but you can't
wander off on your own. Got it.
It's a deal!
I could smell this
caramel from a mile away.
It really sticks to your
teeth, but it's so good!
I've never been so happy.
Hey, guys.
Remember Sanji, our Gourmet?
You know, the one we're here to rescue?
If you keep stopping to munch
on the forest every two seconds,
we're never gonna get anything done.
Yeah, I get that.
But there's awesome desserts everywhere!
What are we supposed to do?
We're in enemy territory!
Food or not, it's no time for a picnic!
Let's search a little more.
But if we don't find Sanji soon, then
we're all headed back to the boat.
What?!
That's not fair!
Tell me you're late!
The river is smelling juice!
Let me try!
Did you, Tia, notice the
bridge is a giant donut?
Okay, you've had enough.
I think it's time we move on.
To the other side!
Mommy!
A crocodile!
Wanna fight? Let's go!
Hold on.
Too bad. Just humans.
What?
We are good enough for you to eat!
Who cares?
The issue here is that we've got
a talking crocodile wearing a hat.
I knew this place was dangerous and weird.
But we've got talking
animals with hats right here.
Come on, you know what I mean.
Let's go back.
I trust Pudding.
She hasn't led us wrong so far.
If we wait by the coast,
she'll bring Sanji to us.
And look at the bridge.
It's only going to get harder.
We'll be fine.
The river's not all that big.
I can jump it.
Oh, why is there another Luffy?
Who the heck are you?
What do you mean, who am I?
I'm Luffy, you big creep!
What's going on?
Two Luffies?
Which one is real?
They move and talk exactly the same!
No, look, not exactly.
It's like he's Luffy's mirror image.
His scar is backwards, and his accessories
and stuff are on the opposite side.
You're right.
It's just like there's
an invisible mirror.
Hey, who are you?
Now me ask you a question.
Now you better answer her.
It's Sochi.
He's right over there.
Huh?
Look, up in the tree.
Hey! Sanji!
Move it!
I hate you!
What are you doing up there?
Say something!
He's running again!
Get back here!
Get out of my way! Faster!
Don't worry about me!
You guys gotta follow Sanji!
Okay, I'm coming too!
Follow the path and do not get separated!
The forest is dangerous, so if it starts
to get weird, turn back and get out!
I'll try to be careful, but I'm
worried we might lose Sanji again!
Sanji!
Nami, go with them!
I'll catch up with you
after I kick this guy's ass!
You got it.
Sanji!
Stop running away from your friends!
All right, come, come!
Mom, tell me, no!
Do it, I'm so sick of you!
What is happening?
There's a giant buried in the ground!
He's huge!
You startled me.
That's our line.
Are you OK, mister?
Who did this to you?
What?
You're buried in the ground.
That's bad.
It's fine.
I want to be buried.
What?
Will you quit messing around?
I am just trying to help you.
Actually, I'd like some juice.
You're ridiculous.
Don't take him seriously, Chopper, or
you'll end up just as crazy as he is.
Wait. Hey, wait.
You guys.
He has something to say.
Ignore him.
By the way, my favorite
is apple juice. So what?
Just keep running.
If you turn left there, you'll
find some apple juice waterfalls.
Those are the best.
We can't lose sight of the plan.
We're just here to rescue Sanji.
This is like a fever dream.
You're looking for someone, aren't you?
He came this way just a
second ago. What? Really?
Chopper, I told you, we got to ignore him.
I can tell you all about what
happened if you bring me some juice.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Hey, Nami, Chopper, watch out! Huh?
Oh!
Whoa!
A rabbit?
Carrot, we should run!
screaming trees talking crocodiles
some kind of murder rabbit I've
had enough this place is too creepy
we know the way back to Luffy let's
go before we get lost well maybe
he was a fake we don't know when we
saw him he just sat there in the tree
staring he never said a word to us
yeah besides if that was the real sanji do
you think he'd keep running away and put
us through this mess let's go back you're
right what the heck
the clock too it's weird
Everyone, watch out!
This looks really bad!
Did you hear?
Hide the way.
Choose, choose, choose.
Plop the path and let them wander.
Time to play.
Time to play a murder game.
Come on, chopper, let's pick up the pace.
This is my max speed.
Is the rabbit here?
Yeah, and he's coming after us fast.
We'll make it back to
Luffy, then escape together.
Got it.
That rabbit is crazy strong.
He's not a meek like me, though
he's not then a Devil Fruit maybe.
Finally they know.
Finally the Straw Hats know
there is nowhere to go.
Now they know we block their way.
Still they run in circles.
When will they give up this game?
It will be long now Soon they will be
her prey Falling right into our trap Lady
Barrel will be pleased Pay the prize
They would make a snack that's so so nice
You see?
He can't use Electro!
It's this!
Be careful! Stay with us! What's that?
Sorry, Mr. Bird!
His lance! Here he comes!
Behind Big Mom's castle,
the Whole Cake Shit, there lies a
body of water called Lake Aprico.
This is a Germa ship.
Permission to enter port.
You may proceed.
Only the fleets of Big Mom's associates,
or those soon to join her empire,
are permitted entry.
Little more!
a bit further almost there all
right that's enough brace for impact
Germa, the name of the world's only
seafaring nation without a land of its own.
It consists of dozens of daunting
vessels that travel independently,
but when they lock But
together, they form a country.
This nautical empire is
ruled by the Vinsmoke family,
who once conquered the
North Blue by force.
This is the Jammah Kingdom.
Their military force, Jammah 666,
is feared by people far and wide.
Nearly all of its inhabitants
are male soldiers.
Its citizens train relentlessly every day.
Just how long do you
plan on sitting there?
Don't be mean.
Shouldn't you be happy to
see your long-lost sister?
Stop saying that.
I cut my ties with you.
I will not repeat myself again.
I have nothing in common with someone
who'd own tasteless art like that.
It's a celebration of our triumph
over the kings in North Blue.
Quite inspiring.
You know,
it's father's dream to
reign over the North
Blue in the name of Germa as he once did.
That's funny, I think that it's natural
for men to be drawn to power and glory.
Why not take advantage of
your royal blood and seize the
day rather than playing pirate
with your silly friends?
Go to hell now!
Now would you talk that way to these
handmaids awaiting your beckon call?
How may we serve young master?
No friggin way!
Why fight your bloodline, dear brother?
War is profitable.
Our business grants us a life of luxury.
Let the minions handle combat.
Does that not sound appealing?
We Vinsmokes have earned that right,
through the sheer power
of our military science.
You have that blood in your veins.
I don't give a damn.
And I am not getting married.
Pudding is a fine woman.
I'm quite fond of her.
Where are you headed, sir?
I'm going to see Sanji.
Leave me be.
Father, what brings you here?
Are you still in here, sulking?
You bastard.
Show some respect, son.
Don't call me your son.
I already have a father, alright?
Seems you roughed up Yonji a bit.
That's a surprise, since
he's rather strong.
I guess that makes me even stronger.
Why don't you meet me outside?
A real man will let his
fists do the talking!
Huh?
Something going on? No!
That guy sure makes a
handy landmark, doesn't he?
Hey!
Did you bring me some juice or not?
The build of lollipops!
Once we go through here, we'll
make it back to Luffy easy!
Out of my way!
Bastard!
Is he still fighting?
Luffy!
We're leaving! Let's go!
Oh, hey!
You're back already?
It's complicated!
Just get moving!
We're in danger!
This place is full of traps! Got it!
Hurry up, Luffy!
There's a weird rabbit trying to kill us!
That's the river where we
saw the talking crocodile!
All right, the exit should be
on the other side of the bridge!
Come on, let's jump!
Chopper, I hope you've got this!
Yeah, that's not a problem!
Just hold on tight!
Hey, watch out!
That's not the real me!
Did you say something, Luffy?
No, it's nothing!
Keep running!
Should be a straight
shot! Almost there! Okay!
What happened to Sanji?
Well, he ran away from us without
a word and he didn't come back.
I mean, it looks like Sanji,
but something's fishy.
I'm not convinced.
We can figure that out after
we make it back to the Sunny.
Right.
We should be in the clear any second now.
Lucky us!
We didn't get lost!
Yeah!
Wait!
What the?
No!
How did this happen?
No enemies this time, right?
Speaking of which, I've got this
thing stuck in my head. No way.
Somehow we just ended up going
around in a big circle. Hold on.
Did you move here just to get in our way?
Oh, my. Don't yell.
It startles me.
And what do you mean, did I move?
I'm, uh, kind of stuck
in the ground over here.
You guys left, and then you
came running right back.
It was kind of weird, actually.
Come on, Chopper.
Let's try again.
Hey, can you pull this out?
Cross the field of lollipops.
Go
over the
river of juice.
This is right, it must be?
Ah!
You startled me!
You keep coming back.
Why is that? Again?
The Log Pose is still going
nuts, but we shouldn't need it.
It's a clear path back to the ship.
How can we get turned around?
It's straight back this way.
Slowly, slowly.
Uh-oh.
Flower?
What?
The trees and flowers can move?
One, two, one, three... The cloud!
It's crawling and talking!
What's going on?
The forest can move?
This is too much!
Oops, they found out! Busted.
If it all moves, there's
no path we can trust.
So you finally figured it out.
This forest is a living nightmare!
Luffy, what are you doing?
Stop it!
We call this place the Seducing Woods.
Nami, watch out!
That's not Luffy! Huh?
Who are you?
You don't know?
Ah, but we've been
together this entire time.
And together we'll stay, because
you'll never escape this forest.
Well, perhaps in a coffin, I suppose.
Bobby, go!
Why don't we all calm down, little Missy?
Look me in the face.
You really must see my old scar.
It's quite ghastly.
Are you, Tia, a tree?
Well, I'm Barrel.
I am not a damn tree.
Barrel?
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl.
What a charming little bunch you are.
When I see such bright and beautiful
faces, why, I can hardly help myself.
I want to dig right in
and scratch them up.
No!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!